how did your mock exam go pretty well i'd say i've had fun this year but i've also studied a lot
such as the life of a senior when i get home i review my lessons and old exam questions
in my spare time i memorize vocabulary and formulas
though my daily grind is tough i do have a singular reprieve
and that's reading manga the highlight of my whole week
he's a double agent but how i never even saw it coming why did this slice of life chapter take a turn
you're killing me
next week can't come soon enough
you
Thank you.
Kono Ha's new chapter.
Um, pardon me.
Did the latest weekly Shino be coming today?
Uh, yeah?
We sold out of it a few minutes ago.
Wanna back order one?
Uh-oh.
Convenience stores always sell out on release day.
But even the bookstore didn't have Kuroha's new chapter.
Why, after thinking about Kuroha all day, have I just died from this disappointment?
Huh? That you, Kono?
Oh, yep, sure is. Hey there. He witnessed my cringiness.
So you came here for the latest weekly Shinobi?
Are you psychic or something?
Don't I wish. I heard you say Konoha's new chapter. And you sounded upset.
Ah!
How embarrassing.
Um, you can have mine, if you'd like.
Hasn't even been cracked open yet.
I can't!
Why? If you're fretting because you're worried about me, please don't.
I'll be fine. Gata would have bought it if it hadn't been the last copy.
I just came in here to kill some time until my bus arrives.
There are lots of bookstores near the station by my house. They can't all be sold out.
Sorry to cut this short, but I should go before I miss my bus.
Wow! Thanks a million!
I'll pay you back first thing tomorrow.
You are so cool. And kind.
The way you helped me out.
You're just like Kono.
Thank you very much.
Awkward.
Did comparing him to one of the characters rub him the wrong way?
Why'd I even open my mouth?
I remind her of a fictional lady?
Does she say that because she thinks I'm effeminate?
Oh, man.
I weirded him out with silly fangirl nonsense.
What?
I guess Yanagi's a fan in his own right.
It's weekly Shinobi release day today.
Kono has been so exciting lately.
I can't put it down.
I can't blame you.
Normally, I'll wait for the full book publication.
But once I read a manga and a magazine,
patience gives way to curiosity.
Every time.
Talk about an odd pair.
I haven't heard that in a while.
No one makes those comments when I'm with Hori's group.
Maybe you aren't, Link?
Are you upset with me?
No, not at all.
It's just, uh...
When I'm by you, girls get jealous.
They just can't fathom why on earth you'd spend time with me.
Eh.
Hmm?
And why is that?
Because you're cool and I'm not?
Cool?
Oh, Remy got a nasty paper cut.
Try thinking about something fun.
Like how school gets out early today.
Yay!
It's gone now.
Don't cry over a harmless little bug.
I'm not crying.
But it's really gone.
You're sure?
You're cooler than me by far.
Wait.
What?
You're not serious, are you?
Because I think everyone would agree you're way cooler.
No, I'd definitely want you around if I got hurt or scared.
How is that relevant?
It doesn't detract from his coolness, but he is strange.
Paper cuts stink.
And I'd rather be described with other adjectives anyway, like cute would be nice.
I noticed you haven't been wearing your glasses lately.
Yeah, they don't look all that good on me.
So I've switched to contacts.
I bet everything looks stunning on that gorgeous face.
If I had a different style, I might wear them more often.
Maybe I'll check out frames after the bookstore.
His delicate features make mine look so homely more than usual.
You're welcome to go along with me.
Go where?
To look at new frames.
New frames?
You really want me along?
Yes, if you aren't busy, of course.
No, I'll come.
He asked so casually.
Who could possibly turn down such a charming invitation?
Hey, I just thought of a funny coincidence.
Not that it means something, but our names are kinds of trees.
Right?
Yanaki and Sakura.
Go for it!
Go, no, wait!
Why are you running?
Do you think they're going to sell out?
Everything does look stunning.
Boy meets girl, boy likes girl, then boy and girl swap bodies!
Ooh, I know that plot line.
Yeah, I read this novel ages ago.
It is such a page-turner.
What's it called?
I'm her and she's me.
Has a TV show and everything.
Huh?
That's the first I've heard of.
What if Hody and Miyamoto swapped bodies?
Toru, pull your head out of your butt and talk sense.
Oh, come on.
Did she break?
Hey!
Someone left their pencil case back in the council room.
Oh, shoe most likely.
Missing pencil case.
Classic Ishikawa!
Pipe down.
You're annoying me, laugh.
What the heck?
Oh, Sengoku, there you are.
We found the owner.
It's one of the second years on next year's council.
Remy's relieved we figured it out.
Oh.
You'll find Sakura online for the cake buffet.
Crams go before we eat cake.
Is she okay, you think?
She's been in La La Land for a hot minute now.
Just leave her be.
I was laughing because Hody switched with you-know-who.
Then Remy and Kono did the same thing.
Not your punching bag.
I'm excited for the cooking class today.
Hey, that's what's up, girl.
What is this?
Trading places gets tricky when nature calls.
And what about bats?
Come back, Yoshikawa.
Join the same side.
What about the restroom, though?
The restroom?
What about it?
It's rough on your kidneys if you hold it in too long.
Just go when you gotta go.
This question's more complex than you comprehend.
Say what?
Don't you ever call me Kyoko,
because it would be creepy and uncomfortable.
Kyoko.
We're here for homework, not to goof off,
so I'm gonna go buy some report paper.
Have a good trip.
While you're there, get some pencil lead.
Okay.
Huh?
I forgot to ask for more red pens!
I didn't think anyone else was in here with me.
Oh.
Um, well...
I'm sorry.
No harm done.
I just walked in as Hody was leaving.
This book is cold.
Huh?
Uh...
Just talking to myself.
It feels that way because your hands are warm.
When the back of his knuckles brushed mine,
I realized just how cold Yanagi's hands are.
Yo, you finished your report?
My hands are cold.
Hmm?
Real cold.
Super duper cold.
Huh?
You're warm enough to me.
And again, I'm a loser.
Hey!
That was not an invitation to get Krabby!
Huh?
You are such a pain!
What'd you expect me to do?
At least Yanagi's gentle when he touches me,
unlike somebody.
Are you invoking a no-touchy rule with me?
That isn't even close to what I said!
You are such a pain!
Like, why is that?
You're giving me the biggest headache right now!
Not even kidding!
Wait!
I thought you were kidding, Toadu!
So, are you warm enough yet?
Mm-hmm.
Warm, but very exhausted.
Because you wrote that report,
you can hit the hay as soon as you get home.
Wanna hold hands?
Not a chance!
I doubt I'll ever understand you.
Toadu's hands are cold, too.
But they warm up pretty quick when he's with me.
Miyamura, you heading out?
Yeah.
I gotta make a stop at the store.
See ya.
Peace.
Man, it's cold.
Huh?
Is this yours?
No, for real.
Sawada,
is there a possibility
that you don't have friends?
Why?
That was a yes-or-no question.
Will you say whether or not
you're being bullied by other students, at least?
I won't stand here and force you to talk,
but it seemed to me
those kids on the second floor
threw your scarf out the window.
If that's what happened,
walk over to me.
Well, all right, then.
Did you say something to them?
Who, me?
I didn't say a single word.
He mouthed rot in hell, ugly cows!
Who does that nosy nobody think he is?
So,
you are being bullied to some extent.
Hmm.
At first,
I thought we just had a difference of opinion.
And out of nowhere,
they started ignoring me.
Sounds about right.
You act like you know how it feels.
But someone with your friend group
could never relate!
It just took time.
It's not like I went around
begging each of them to be my friend.
Keep your chin up.
Things will get better.
If those idiots are gonna ignore you,
ignore them right back.
Know why?
Because the ones with any brains
will be begging to be your friends eventually.
And you'll be the winner.
But,
does winning even have a point?
I figured you'd wanna win.
I don't care.
I forgot to tell you
that I stepped on your scarf.
Stop!
It was an accident!
Sawada's, like,
really tight with the seniors.
Guess her classmates aren't as fun
to talk to as the older kids are.
Yeah, I bet that's what she thinks.
So stuck up.
She's right behind us.
Yikes.
Why's that an issue?
It's not that I don't want
to get along with them.
It's that I don't really know
how to go about it.
So simply being in class
makes me self-conscious.
This wind is crazy!
Slow down!
I love my hair!
So chilly!
It's too cold to be up here
in this breezeway, Sawada!
Come in where it's warm!
What are you doing out there?
Do you think I'm weird?
Well, duh!
But being kind of weird is awesome!
Did something happen?
Not exactly, no.
Just think,
if you're in the weird side
of the spectrum,
what does that make this girl?
Here, this candy will cheer you off!
Stag Beetle candy tastes like
Stag Beetles too!
Please don't feel obligated
to accept it.
Huh?
Oh, um, no, I want to try them.
Aha!
The power of Stag Beetles!
Said no one besides you.
Apart from being weird,
do you think I'm a little too tight
with you seniors?
Maybe, but why is that an issue?
Because I don't really have people
I'd consider friends
in my own grade.
Oh, I can see why that's rough.
Every class has to incorporate group work
and girls form quick so fast.
Yeah, they do!
Mm-hmm.
In a nutshell,
that's what it is.
So, Ada,
does the friend thing
stem from classroom drama?
Are you okay?
Well, it's difficult,
but I'm powering through.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You can vent any time.
We'll listen to whatever
you have to say.
Hearing you out
is about all we can do
since we aren't in your class,
but it's better than nothing, right?
Pour your heart out!
Thank you so much!
Up for sampling
some drone beetle chocolate?
Tastes like drone beetles!
Please don't feel obligated
to accept it.
I'm not really comfortable
in my class,
but school's not all that bad.
Any suggestions
for where to post this?
I'd say the bulletin board
if we thought
to reserve any space.
Well...
Shimoda!
Huh?
Do you know of any free spots
on bulletin boards?
Yeah,
there's one at the main entrance.
We'll endure the wrath
of the third years
if we post there.
Really?
Recruiting for clubs
seems like quite the challenge.
I never knew till now.
Then guess what happened?
Sawada!
So you were trying
to fix that poster?
Technically,
it's supposed to fit
within the frame.
Oh!
This must be the thumbtack
that fell out!
I'm sure.
They couldn't push
far enough
into the hardwood.
Hey, listen.
That poster?
It belongs to some
girls I know.
My fr...
F...
Fellow?
Yeah!
My fellow classmates
hand-painted
that sign themselves.
Said they're having
trouble recruiting.
They made it big
in order to catch
people's attention,
I think.
So, um...
Maybe...
You could leave it
where it is?
It's coming down.
But I'm gonna need
a chair.
Wanna grab one
from the home ec room?
It's right over there.
Is it even unlocked?
Take it down!
Stand aside, Prez!
Yeah, right.
You can't reach it either.
Don't move!
They look like a family
on their day off.
Stay strong, Sengoku.
There.
It's off.
Now let me down!
Nice teamwork, you guys.
Next stop!
What next stop?
Where are you taking me?
We're done!
Mission accomplished!
You're heavy.
Then hurry and let me go!
Here we are!
The main entrance.
May I see the sign?
I'll post it.
What?
Yes, its size is eye-catching,
but what good does that do
if it's in a secluded spot?
Let's move that one to the right.
And then these two.
And there should be space.
Hmm?
I thought this bulletin board
was off-limits to us second years.
Why's that?
Well, because third years
are the only ones who ever use it.
The main entrance is a shared space.
We won't get in trouble
for using this board?
Of course not.
I guess we need to make our own sign
that clarifies all students
can post here no matter their year.
Nice.
Now every student coming through those doors
will be sure to see in.
Hope it gets some people
to check out their club.
Let me make senpai!
You're the absolute best!
Sengoku!
Thank you.
Anytime.
Oh!
Want some candy?
Alright now.
How about some stag beetle chocolate?
That's for sure.
Tell me about it.
Hey, Sawada.
So is it true?
Did you really take our poster down
and then re-hang it
on a whole other board?
Shimura said he saw you do it
two days ago
after school let out.
He saw me?
Um, okay.
Signs can't overlap
the bulletin board's frame
and yours did.
So I moved it somewhere
it wouldn't break any rules.
Except it wasn't even my idea.
A first year came by
to check out the club.
But that's the only bite
we've gotten so far.
Still,
that was our first first year
to show interest.
I was like,
what?
When they said
they saw the poster.
And I was really glad too.
Thanks for your help,
Sawada.
I hope the next one
who sees it
actually joins.
Before I forget,
is it also true
that you rode
on the student council
president's shoulders
to get around the school?
Ah!
No!
Well,
I mean,
yes,
that did happen.
So the leader
of the student body
is your minion
slash vehicle of choice?
No way!
And you're related
to that bird here
with piercings?
All lies!
guys!
Hiiist deles!
Xoyang, Shnobuukuroi Kage
Hikari wo yadoise close ayiba
Mamoruwa koudoku ikufoza wa ni
I'll see you next time.